Hey, what's going on guys? Beautiful box
art on here as always from Katoki San
with all the markings on there. You do
love to see water slides, but it is a
rather large water slide decal sheet
here. All right, guys. Here is this
massive kit all built up inside. You can
open that up. There's our pilot figure
in there. Here on the side of the arm
while we're here, that opens up and
[music] we've got missiles there on that
side. But obviously our missiles up
there as well. Also here on the chest,
this of course opens up as well on both
sides. of times in Gundam full armor
doesn't always necessarily mean [music]
full like armor. It's armor and
armaments like in case of the unicorn
for example. People often point out that
it's called full armor unicorn when it
doesn't actually add any armor to it. It
just adds a bunch of armaments. Yeah, it
is basically like getting the same kit
again in just a like a kind of a
different combination. But I have to say
if you don't have any of those kits,
then it's [clears throat] definitely a
great opportunity to pick up this kit.
The kit on its own is awesome. I mean, I
guess that is one point worth giving
Bandai some props for the fact that it's
not the P-Bandai kit. This kit could
have very well been and probably should
have been a premium Bandai release as
well, but the fact that it's not is is a
nice change of pace every now and then,
so.